Add a basic Notepad application. Focus on minimum viable product. It should have:

- Text field to allow user input of text and highlight text
- Bold, italic, underline icons in the header which can be toggled on-off and affect text that is written or highlighted
- File > Save should allow the user to name a ".notepad" file and save it to the desktop
- Have a shortcut on the desktop and in start menu to launch the application
- Have a win95 style icon
